# **Kevin Gerstner**



☑ sirkevinicus@gmail.com



314-614-2301

# **Work Experience**

#### **Graphic Design Intern @ ArchCity Defenders**

MAY 2019 - AUG 2019 \\ SAINT LOUIS, MO

- » Created a digital art collection of clients using Photoshop for print and web marketing.
- » Illustrated graphics that were featured on the companies' social media pages.
- » Researched social justice issues and communicated key issues to affected communities.

#### Research Assistant @ University of Tulsa

OCT 2018 - APR 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Researched and co-authored a paper on the topic of HCI and Gender with Prof. Sandeep Kuttal entitled: "Remote Pair-Programming in Online CS Education: Investigating through a Gender Lens". The paper was presented in the 2019 VL/HCC (Visual Languages & Human Centric Computing) conference.

#### Game Navigator & Server @ Shuffles Board Game Café

SEP 2018 - JAN 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Taught groups of people how to play board games, as well as taking orders and delivering food. In my spare time, I read rule books to learn new games.

# **Projects**

#### **Portfolio Website**

Web Developer \\ 2021 \\ www.kevingerstner.com

- » Designed and coded a portfolio website using HTML, CSS/SASS, Bootstrap 5, and JS
- » Used web-friendly standards like Responsive Design and Lighthouse Analytics

#### **Tomb of Khaibit**

#### Environment Designer & Tools Programmer \\ 2021

- » Coded a Unity editor tool that can make procedurally generated dungeons
- » Designed and implemented game systems such as a Spell Tree, Puzzles, & Enemies
- » Made pixel art for the tomb environment using Aseprite

#### **Song Pong**

#### Feature Developer & Artist \\ 2020

- » Made a rhythm game based on Pong in three months with the Unity engine
- Coded features like spawning notes along to the beat and a Song Editor
- » Created art assets in Illustrator and Blender

#### **Knock-Out! Global Smackdown Board Game**

#### Board Game Designer & Artist \\ 2018

- » Created over 150 unique card illustrations, box art, and graphics for marketing
- » Created a Wordpress website
- » Launched a Kickstarter campaign

# **Summary**

Imaginative and meticulous developer and designer with experience creating websites using HTML, SASS, JS, and jQuery. Will graduate in 2021 with a B.S. in Computer Science and Art & Math minors. Experience leading projects in agile development & picks up new skills quickly. Excels at motivating self and others in a team.

### Skills

#### **Technologies**

HTML • CSS/SASS • jQuery • JavaScript • C# • Java • C++

#### **Tools & Platforms**

Netlify • WordPress • itch.io • Unity • Visual Studio • GitHub • ClickUp • Eclipse

#### Design

Photoshop • Illustrator • InDesign • Figma • Aseprite

# **Education**

# The University of Tulsa 2017 - 2021 \\ TULSA, OK

B.S. in Computer Science and B.S. in Computer Simulation and Gaming with Math and Art minors. 3.8 GPA

# **Certifications**

Unity Certified Associate Game Developer

# Interests

Board Games, Overwatch, Art, Animated movies, Horror Games, Music, Coffee Tasting